Stop!!
What just happened?
I'm so sorry, Big Brother...
Because of me, you...
It's not your fault, Sarah.
Don't worry about it.
When I felt like,
I wanted to save you,
fire shot out of my body.
Am I sick?
You're not sick, Sarah!
Damn it...
What is happening to her?
What's going to happen to me?
I'm scared, Big Brother!
I'm so scared!
No matter what happens,
I'll protect you.
Don't worry, Sarah.
Big Brother!
S-Sarah!
Sarah!
Big Brother!
Big Brother...
S-Sarah?
Why didn't you save me?
You promised
you would protect me!
Damn it...
That same dream again.
EPISODE 7
CROWING OVER A FEATHER
I want to play in the sand too!
Piyoko, Keiji's having a sand bath.
Huh?
Chickens sand bathe to remove bugs
and impurities from our feathers.
The same way humans bathe
to stay clean and healthy.
Oh...
However, I opt for
a more sophisticated method.
I use this!
Bug spray for female chickens!
An elegant woman must opt
for an elegant solution!
Oh...
Uh, excuse me...
Are you the chickens
who fight against Demons?
How do you know that?
I knew it!
Whoa! Awesome!
We've seen you
on the human's phones.
You're even famous
in the pigeon world!
We're seeing them in real lfe!
They're so cool!
Um, If you say so...
This is kind of making me blush...
Oh! Why don't we ask him?
What?
There's no way he'd accept!
It seems like he's with his family.
It won't hurt to ask...
Uh, would you be interested...
...in joining us for a group date?
A group date?
You mean one of those
things human males and females do?
Yes! They're very popular
in the pigeon world right now.
P-Popular?!
I had no idea...
Our third had to go on
a last-minute carrier pigeon job,
so he just canceled.
So we were wondering
if you'd be interested
in joining us in his place?
Me?
Honestly, I 'm not interested in pigeons.
Please, just come with us!
With you there,
there will be so much to talk about!
Plus, I think the ladies would
love to talk to a hero!
Please, just come for a little bit!
Sounds like fun.
Keiji, you should go with them.
W-Well, if you all insist...
I guess I can go
for a little.
- Thank you very much!
What?!
Why is there a chicken here?
What a bummer.
Looks like this meet-up's a dud.
This isn't what you promised.
S-Sorry! Huh, that's weird!
You don't recognize him?
He's the famous rooster
who fights monsters!
- Never heard of him.
Anyways, chickens can't fly.
That's not cool.
They go "kokekokko"
and it's kind of weird.
What's that dangling from his chin?
Gross!
What did you say?!
Hey you!
Don't tease the Mister!
Piyoko, calm down.
Keiji, listen up.
To be honest,
I can't stand hearing them
slandering us like that.
I'm steaming mad!
It really makes my crown curl!
But Keiji, no violence.
This is a group date.
The battlefield is a social one.
So we need to woo them
on this date
by showing them
how awesome chickens truly are.
That's how we win.
I see.
So it all rests on my shoulders.
Leave it to me.
My pride as a chicken is
on the line in this battle...
I mean date.
I'll use my undeniable appeal and
make them fall in love with me!
Uh...?
Go get 'em, Mister!
- Something seems off.
- Go get 'em, Mister! Go get 'em!
- I hope he'll be all right.
- Go get 'em, Mister!
Let's start with intros!
I'm Ken!
I'm Masa. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ann.
I'm Seiko.
I'm Marin. Nice to meet you.
My...
Name is...
Ah! Keiji!
You are so cool, Mister!
Not cool.
Cringe.
Gross.
I should have seen this coming.
Wow!
Amazing, you're a racing pigeon!
We pigeons have
an instinctual sense of direction,
so I can fly out a 100 kilometers
and still find my way home.
Now's your chance to
show them what you've got!
Uh, okay!
Chickens are great too, you know!
We get up early and our voices are loud.
That is so annoying in the
morning!
It's so loud, huh?
Something else! Something else!
We run fast!
Flying is faster...
Yup.
Doesn't seem too efficient.
- I know!
We have big crowns!
Crowns aren't really that necessary!
We forget about bad things
in three seconds!
I don't think it's just
about the bad things.
Ugh. He doesn't seem too smart.
I'm a hard pass on a
lack of smarts.
Agreed!
This is getting more
and more unbearable.
I feel kind of bad for him.
That's enough!
I don't care what
you think about chickens.
As long as I live a life with pride,
that's all that matters.
I'll walk the path I choose.
That's all I can do.
- So cool!
I've never met such a manly bird!
I've been looking for a man
just like him!
If you look close,
he's actually hot.
Huh? What?
I...don't really get it...
Is this what they call...
A walk-off home run?!
Will you go out with me?
No, me!
Marry me!
- Hey! The Mister is my husband!
- Please!
What is going on here?
Well, ya got me here...
- Please!
- Hey, marry me!
He's a man whore.
Y-You sold me out!
- The worst.
- Scum.
Trash.
- Too bad.
- What a letdown.
I feel horrible. I'm sorry.
I don't know what came over me earlier.
It's nothing.
They were just pigeons anyway.
What is going on with me?
Elizabeth!
Next time I won't forgive you!
Got it?!
Make sure to keep her safe
next time, okay?
What are you going to do now?
Run, Keisuke.
- After him!
- No, wait.
Even if we let him go, we have a hostage.
He'll be back
sooner or later.
I'll come back for you, Father!
Please hold on!
What are you doing, Elizabeth?
I'm making lunch.
Hey!
I've seen this fish before!
It's the same one
that was on Pop's back!
It's called a carp, Piyoko.
Line caught?
Absolutely not.
I just sent a current through a location
in the pond where I though carp would be.
Easy, right?
I didn't know you could do that.
Looks like fun!
I wanna do that too!
Can I do it too?
Hmm...
It might be a few months
too soon for you.
I can catch a carp too,
you know!
I'll use this—
Like I said, it's too soon for you.
I'll overlook this for now...
Oh! There's something just right
for her to do over there...
Piyoko...
Could you please pick me three
dandelion flowers for me over there?
I want to add them to the food.
Flowers to decorate our food, right?
That's easy peasy!
Flowers... flowers...
There are so many flowers,
aren't there?
Huh?
These flowers are small and cute,
just like me!
I'll get these!
Those are flowers too, Piyoko...
But...
The dandelions that
I wanted you to get are these.
I just took a side route
and I was going to
get those flowers later on!
If you got them already,
then I guess this was all pointless!
The last step is to season it
with salt and pepper, and...
...it's done!
White fish saute with a
two-tone vegetable sauce,
and a dandelion garnish.
Yay! I love fish!
Is it edible?
How rude!
Cooking is one of my talents,
okay?!
I mean, how good can it be?
Delicious!!!
What is this? The vegetable sauce
perfectly complements the carp,
neutralizing the fishiness
while drawing out full-bodied flavor!
It tastes just like the time
I ate a grasshopper
and a frog at the same time...
and a revolution occured
on my tastebuds! It's better than that!
I'm a genius!
Let's eat!
Wait!
I have the smallest portion!
What?! They're the same size!
Nope! This corner on
this one is missing!
Don't be greedy!
The only thing small here,
is your character!
Just be grateful you're
getting a portion!
Give me another half,
then I'll be grateful!
- Hey! Don't mess around!
- Let me eat more!
- Absolutely not!
Let me eat more!
Hey, Mister, I'm not hungry,
so you can have mine!
Oh, thank you !!
Huh?
You'd eat a child's portion?!
You scum!
So delicious!!
Spit it back out right now!
No can do!
So? Any more info
on the White Demon?
No.
There's nothing
since his last appearance.
I haven't found any new leads since.
All we can do right now is head
to where he was last sighted.
We might find a clue there.
We still have
at least 250 kilometers to go...
Huh?
Come to think of it...
Where's Piyoko?
What?! Only one bug?
We told you to catch ten,
didn't we?
You messin' with us, huh?!
C-Catching ten is impossible!
Please forgive me!
Is there some reason
why you can't follow my orders?
You know what happens now,
don't you?!
Die!
Hold it!
Are you hurt?
N-No!
Who the hell are you?!
Hmph!
Me, you say?
I'm "Dutiful Piyoko"!
DUTY
I live by Pops' credo and
I never let evil off the hook!
My entrance is spot on!
So this little chick wants to fight us?
Fine. I'm happy to oblige.
We're gonna kill you!
Phew! Think twice before
doing anything bad ever again, got it?
Damn it. I'm not done here!
Do it! I dare you!
Kiss my butt!
Unforgiveable!
You're not getting away with this!
Huh?
Demon alert issued.
- Demon alert issued.
- Get back here!
Danger.
- Evacuate the area immediately.
- Get back here, you brat!
Stop right now, you brat!
I'm not stopping!
Come back here!
P-Pops!
You're a billion years too green
to face off against me!
Huh?!
Was that—?
Are you hurt, Piyoko?
Wait... Piyoko?
Why am I so weak?
Why can't I be useful
for the Mister, like Elizabeth?
I always need to be saved.
Hey, Mister, I'm not hungry
so you can have mine!
I know full well...
...that that's all I can offer.
I know I'm useless and
nothing more than dead weight.
But I don't want to be that!
I don't want to be a burden to him!
Maybe...
...my time with him is coming to an end.
Is her stomach upset?
I think she might be
depressed about something.
Keiji...
I've been a little concerned
about something.
We've been with Piyoko
for about a month now...
DUTY
But she hasn't grown at all.
Any way you look at it,
isn't that strange?
So, you noticed too.
Who the hell are you?
I...
I finally found you...
Big...
... Brother.
A-Are you all right?!
W-What did he...
...just say?!
It's finally time for the
Goshikidori Family to make our entrance.
But Keisuke, this town feels
dangerous.
Next time:
Not All Feathers Hold a Song.
Oh, I've located a lady!
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS